(忆往昔)
我是唐娜·汉斯姆警长
I'm sheriff Donna Hanscum.
我丈夫道格去年离开我了
My husband, Doug, left me last year.
他说我喜欢饼干奶昔
'cause he said I loved cookie-dough milkshakes
-多过喜欢他  -你值得更好的
- more than him. - You deserve better.
-唐娜  -道格
- Donna. - Doug.
你可真漂亮啊
Well, aren't you looking good?
我减了6磅呢
I lost 6 pounds.
你已经成功四分之一了
You're 1/4 of the way there!
道格看上去像个混蛋
Doug seems like kind of a dick.
你有想过世上有一些东西...
You ever think there are things out there
一些...不曾被警察记录在案的东西吗
things that...don't end up in the police blotter?
我觉得我看见了...牙齿
What I think I saw... were teeth.
-你觉得我疯了吧  -完全不会
- You think I'm crazy?  - Not at all.
-她突然就抽出把刀  -丘斯警长是吸血鬼
- She just pulled out a machete. - Sheriff Cuse is a vampire.
唐娜看到了他的牙齿
Donna saw his teeth.
什么鬼  吸血鬼
What the cuss?! A vampire?!
他们伤不了你  他们伤不了你
They can't hurt you. They can't hurt you.
会流血的怪物就能被杀死
If it bleeds, you can kill it.
这不是因为你害怕小丑  是吧
This isn't about your, uh, your clown thing, is it?
什么  当然不是
What? No.
它们到底把你怎么了
What in the world did they do to you?
我觉得我看到了些幻觉
I think I've been having visions.
就是一些画面  更像是感觉吧
It's just images. I mean, more of a feeling, really.
或许这幻觉是上帝给的
I mean, maybe these visions are coming from God.
迪恩  第一个幻觉是我祈祷后看到的
I mean, Dean, the first one happened after I prayed.
你祈祷了  什么时候
You prayed? When was this?
在医院的时候
Back in the hospital.
你祈祷什么了
What did you pray about?
我想我就是在寻求答案
I guess I was just looking for answers, you know?
上帝什么时候回应过我们的祈祷了
When was the last time God answered any one of our prayers?
(如今)
这是加时赛的第二次跑垒得分了
This is their second drive in overtime,
两队都曾持球
with both teams having possessed the ball.
下一分便能定胜局
The next score wins.
一举一动都...
Every play becomes...
32码线处的1号和10号
1st and 10 from the 32-yard line.
斯坦
Stan!
你能扔下垃圾吗
Can you take out the trash?
他往左跑了  天呐...
He is running left. Ohh! He gets...
简直臭死了
Stinks to high heaven.
是你的厨艺太差
It's your cooking that stinks.
你说什么  亲爱的
What was that, honey?
没什么  亲爱的
Nothing, dear.
打加时赛呢  等等的吧
The game's in O.T., can't it wait?
将他逼回中心  慢慢防守...
...Backs him into center, slowly defends...
亲爱的  再给我拿瓶啤酒
Hey, hon, bring me another Brewski.
他被赶出了袋形区
He's flushed out of the pocket.
谢了  亲爱的
Hey, thanks, babe.
还说不用设负鼠陷阱
Don't need possum traps, huh?
[邪恶力量 第11季第7集]
那个
So, uh...
万一你还真在听
on the off chance that you're actually listening, uh...
我要说实话
I gotta be real honest.
那些幻象我实在想不明白
The visions aren't making a whole lot of sense to me.
事实上
Truth is...
我搞不清状况
I don't know what's what.
求你了
Please.
你究竟想告诉我什么
What are you trying to say?
不是吧
Really?
-你不是吧  -你知不知道什么叫隐私啊
- I mean, really? - You ever hear of privacy?
你要隐私就关门啊
Hey, you want privacy, close your door.
我们不是谈过这事了吗
Thought we talked about this.
是的  迪恩  但你为什么这么不愿相信
Yeah, we did, Dean. But why is it so hard to believe
上帝在让我看到一些关于
that God could be sending me visions
-黑暗的幻觉  -开玩笑吗
- about the Darkness? - You kidding me?
天启的时候他都没出现
He didn't feel the need to show up for the apocalypse.
现在为什么就会在乎了
Why would he give a crap now?
我不知道  或许因为那是他妹妹
I don't know. Maybe because she's his sister?
你想怎么办  坐视不管  不理会他吗
What do you wanna do? Sit back? Ignore him? Do nothing?
不  我不是那个意思
No, that's... that's not what I'm saying.
我的意思是  别指望上帝
I'm saying, don't count on God.
指望我们自己
Okay? Count on us.
好吧
Right.
这是小卡在加沙找到的一切
Oh, this is everything Cass dug up in Gaza,
所有的圣经前传说
every last bit of prebiblical lore.
一半都没法看  是阿拉姆语
Half of it I couldn't read. It's in Aramaic.
另一半
And the other half...
没什么用
nada.
完全没提到黑暗
Not a single mention of the Darkness, so...
我勒个去
Well, I'll be damned.
唐娜  你好吗
Donna, what's shakin'?
吸脂怪事件那个唐娜吗
Fat sucker Donna?
什么叫"杀人兔"
What do you mean "killer bunny"?
(明尼苏达州  卡蒂奇格罗夫)
(明尼苏达州  卡蒂奇格罗夫  拉森郡警局)
警长
Sheriff.
见到你俩太棒了
You two are a sight for sore eyes!
你辖区扩大了吗
What, are you working all 10,000 lakes now?
这不是你平时的管辖区域
This isn't usually your beat.
只管拉森郡  因为裁员了嘛
Just Larsen County, what with the cutbacks and all.
整体来说还是像美食一样美好的
For the most part, it's been tater tots and lemon drops,
除了这件事
except for this doozy.
接到报案说有复活节兔子杀人
I mean, when you get a call about a killer Easter bunny,
简直不知道该怎么想
you don't know what to think.
想这事太疯狂了
Well, you think crazy.
而且那人挺健壮的
Guy's real strong, too.
冲撞了好几个警官
Lashed out at several officers.
一整队人合力才把他关起来
Took a whole team just to get him into custody.
但这还不是最怪的地方
But that's not the weirdest part...
那颗兔子头  拿不下来
bunny head won't come off.
什么意思
What do you mean?
除了上电锯什么都试了
Tried everything short of a chainsaw,
但就是取不下来
but it's really stuck.
谁知道呢  可能没什么的
I mean, who knows? Could be nothing.
或许那人的头像我叔叔沃利一样大
Guy could just have a big melon like my uncle Wally.
但自从我知道晚上都有什么妖魔鬼怪出没后
But ever since I've seen what goes bump in the night...
我实在不想冒险
I'm not taking any chances.
你做得很对
You did the right thing, for sure.
或许吧
Maybe.
我还不完全确定这事是我们的范畴内的
I'm just still not 100% sure this is our kind of case.
但如果你这儿有只野兔(兔八哥)的话
But if, uh, you got a wild hare...
听懂我的意思了吧
See what I did there?
见到你俩太高兴了
It's good to see you two!
这是谁啊  警长
Who you got there, sheriff?
两位  这是斯托弗警官
Gentlemen, this is Officer Stover.
他负责这桩案子
He's lead on the case.
我们是艾略特和萨维奇探员
Agents Elliott and Savage.
见到你很高兴  叫我道格就好
Nice to meet ya. And please, call me Doug.
这两位先生会在兔子案上帮忙
These two fine fellas will be helping out with the old hippity hop.
我们会需要帮助的
We're gonna need it.
倒不是说汉斯姆警长做得有什么不好
And not that Sheriff Hanscum isn't doing a bang-up job.
有她在是我们的荣幸
We're lucky to have her.
那我回去工作了
Well, I better get back to it.
怎么了
What?
这不关我们的事
Hey, it's none of our business,
但某人似乎喜欢上某人了
but it looks like somebody might have a crush.
我是晚上出生的  迪恩  但不是昨晚
I was born at night, Dean. Not last night.
怎么了  他似乎挺好的
What's the deal? He seems nice.
他是挺好
He is!
但他是警察  还叫道格
But he's a cop... Named Doug.
我显然是有固定的类型
I mean, clearly, I have a type,
但不要再犯错了
but no, thank you, ma'am.
一朝被狗咬  十年怕道格
Won't be once bitten, twice Doug'd.
好了  那只兔子呢
All right, where's the Wascally Wabbit?
有目击证人吗
Any witnesses?
有  被害人妻子  芙兰·辛克尔
Yeah, vic's wife... Fran Hinkle.
可怜人以为她要下个没命
Poor thing thought she was next,
但兔子就直接起来出门了
but the bunny just up and walked out the door.
-确认他身份了吗  -没有
- You I.D. Him yet? - Nope.
没有钱包  没有电话
No wallet. No cell.
查了指纹  但没有前科
Ran his prints, but no prior record.
都没法控制他足够久
Couldn't even get our hands on him long enough
查看有没有什么明显标记
to check for any identifying marks.
我们只知道  他是白人
Only thing we do know... he's caucasian,
大概18到25岁之间
roughly 18 to 25.
而且很吓人
And terrifying.
克莱夫打来了  说是急事
Clive's on the line. Said it's an emergency.
如果需要我  说一声
Just shoot a hoot if you need me.
需要什么吗  油煎饼
You need anything? Crullers?
现在不用
Not right now.
你好吗  哥们
What's up, doc?
如果你能开口会容易得多
Be easier all around if you just talk to us.
-小心  -嗯
- Careful. - Yeah.
怎么回事  伙计
So what happened, pal?
摇头丸吃多了吗
What, you dropped too much molly?
把面具用超级胶水粘在头上了
Super glue your mask to your head,
然后偏执发作  就捅死个人
get paranoid, stab a guy?
我也经历过啊
I've been there.
我猜猜  兔子罗杰
Let me guess, Rog.
你是被陷害了
You were framed!
怎么了
What?
迪恩
Dean!
我能行  我没事
I-I got it. I got it.
-不是恶魔  -他真有劲
- It's not a demon. - He is strong.
好吧
All right.
(明尼苏达理工大学)
永远爱凯莉
"Kylie forever."
这个能用
That'll work.
最好是她
Better be her.
名单上最后一个凯莉了
Last Kylie on the list.
打扰  凯莉·詹宁斯吗
Excuse me. Kylie Jennings?
嗯
Yes?
认识这只兔子吗
You know this rabbit?
-你们找到他了  -他是谁
- You found him. - Who is he?
迈克·胡克斯  我男朋友
Mike Hooks. He's my boyfriend.
好吧  那你知道你男朋友为什么
Okay, well, you have any idea why your boyfriend
要捅死人吗
would stab somebody?
等等  什么
Wait. What?
迈克和斯坦·辛克尔怎么认识的
How would Mike know Stan Hinkle?
-谁  -被害人
- Who? - The victim.
等等  这没道理啊
Okay, hold on. This... This makes no sense.
迈克为什么要捅死一个陌生人
Why would Mike stab a complete stranger? I mean...
-天呐  -怎么了
- Oh, God. - What?
我不知道  我本以为没什么
I don't know. I thought it was nothing,
但他昨天怪怪的
but he was acting really weird yesterday.
怎么怪了
Weird how?
我们下课后去了一间旧货店
Well, after class, we went to this thrift shop.
要为校外的一个派对买服装
We needed to buy costumes for a party off-campus.
迈克找到一个特别吓人的兔子面具
And Mike found this super creepy bunny mask.
我简直恶心死了  但他特别喜欢
I mean, it... it grossed me out, which he just loved.
但他一戴上
But as soon as he put it on...
就开始怪了吗
That's when the weird started?
嗯  他...盯着我
Yeah. He just... stared at me.
起初我以为他是在胡闹
At first, I thought that he was just messing around,
但他直接走出了商店  都没付钱
but then he walked out without paying.
而且还把手机留在了收银台
He left his cell at the register,
我也没办法联系他
so I had no way of reaching him, and...
迈克人可好了
Look, Mike's, like, the sweetest, okay?
但我告诉你们  他一戴上那个面具
But I'm telling you, as soon as he put that mask on,
他就像变了个人
it's like he was a completely different person.
你真觉得医院能把这东西取下来吗
You really think the hospital can get this puppy off?
俩字  骨锯
Two words... bone saw.
好了
Yeah, let's see here...
怎么了
What?
女警就干不了重活儿吗
Lady cops can't handle the heavy liftin'?
我没那个意思
I didn't mean that...
我就是觉得
I just figured...
我们给他打了一堆镇静剂
We shot him full of tranquilizers.
他很沉啊
Dead weight.
我怕你伤到自己
I didn't want you to hurt yourself.
伤到自己
"Hurt myself"?
我可是有锻炼的
I do crossfit.
激发内心潜能  用膝盖去抬
Just gotta engage the core and lift with the knees.
看好了
Watch and learn.
帮帮忙能死啊
Little help would be nice!
好吧
Okay, yeah.
嗯  等等
Yeah. Oh, hold up.
是联调局的
Those FBI boys.
好啊  迪恩
Hiya, Dean.
你没事吧
You okay?
有事
No, not really.
一个19岁的孩子死了
A 19-year-old kid is dead.
这不怪你或道格
That's not on you or Doug.
他是在尽职
He was just doing his job.
我知道  但是
I know, but...
这孩子是无辜的
That kid was innocent.
如果面具被诅咒了
I mean, if the mask was cursed,
那他就只是傀儡  对吗
then he was just a puppet, right?
他也是受害者
He was victim, too.
再不会有别人死了
No one else dies.
不会再这样死了
Not like this.
加油
Come on.
很好
That's good.
来  再来一个
Come on, one more.
很好
Good.
很好  巴克纳  你的努力都会有回报的
Nice job, Buckner. All your hard work's gonna pay off.
-你真这么觉得  教练  -我确定
- You think so, coach? - I know so.
球探不要你就是他傻
Any scout would be a damn fool not to snatch you up.
别吃生长激素了
Just lay off the H.G.H.
你可能得做药检
You might have to pee in a cup.
如果还需要练习  我就在隔壁
I'll be next door if you need another spot.
(卡蒂奇格罗夫高中  球场小丑)
需要再来一次吗
Need another spot?
(犯罪现场  止步)
好消息  教练还活着
Good news... coach is still alive.
坏消息  他陷入昏迷了
Bad news... he's in a coma,
所以还不算没事了
so we're not out of the woods yet.
连着两天两个戴面具的疯子
Two masked psychos in two days.
太巧了吧
I mean, what are the chances?
我猜是模仿犯
My guess? Copycat killer.
都怪社交网络
Damn social media.
好吧
Okay?
-嗯  -嗯
- Yeah. - Yeah.
你们跟那孩子谈过了吗
You know, did you guys talk to the kid yet?
-请便  -谢谢
- Be my guest. - Thanks.
艾略特和萨维奇探员
Agents Elliott and Savage.
布洛克·巴克纳
Brock Buckner.
布洛克  你看到了什么
Well, um, Brock, what did you see?
没看到多少  我当时正在锻炼二头肌
Not much, man. I mean, I was just hammering my bi's,
练得正起劲  紧接着
gettin' all swole, and next thing I know,
就看到埃文斯教练被吉祥物打趴了
Coach Evans is getting his ass kicked by the mascot.
吉祥物是谁
And who is the mascot?
我怎么会知道  我是四分卫
Why would I know? I'm the quarterback.
而且  他的面具摘不下来
Besides, his mask wouldn't come off.
而且他强壮得难以置信
I couldn't believe how strong he was either.
他长得那么瘦  却跟我一样有劲
I mean, for a scrawny dude, he was as strong as me,
我可是州举重冠军
and I hold the state bench record.
是吗  你举多少
Oh, yeah? What do you bench?
四块盘
Four plates.
每边四块
On each side.
挺厉害
That's...
除了面具摘不掉
Okay, so other than the, uh, mask not coming off
小丑变身绿巨人
and the jester hulking out,
你还注意到其他奇怪之处了吗
did you notice anything else unusual?
什么意思
What do you mean?
电涌  温度变化
Uh, power surges? Temperature fluctuations?
举重室之前的确突然冷了下来
Uh, the weight room did get really cold.
谢谢
Thanks.
好吧
Well...
不是诅咒物件
ain't a cursed object.
-是鬼魂附身  -老天爷
- Ghost possession. - Oh, for jeez.
-鬼能附身人  -是啊
- Ghosts can possess people? - Yeah.
鬼魂基础知识
So, uh, ghosts 101...
一个人的灵魂可以附在一件
Somebody's spirit can attach itself to an object
或多件其遗留下来的物件上
or a bunch of objects left behind.
在这件案子里  就是面具
In this case, masks.
嗯  那么拿到物件的人
Right, so whoever possesses the object...
就会被附身
Gets possessed.
但如果我们不能把面具取下来
But if we can't get the mask off,
要怎么打破附身啊
how the heck do ya unpossess someone?
一切事物都有弱点  鬼魂也有
Everything has a weakness, even ghosts.
他们讨厌铁和盐
They hate iron and salt.
我们只需要用盐来
So all we gotta do is spook the spook
吓唬一下鬼魂  或许可以给撬下来
with a little salt and, uh, maybe we could pry it off.
我的节食秘密
My diet secret.
咬一口甜点  就往上撒盐
One bite of dessert and then I dump salt on it.
立刻没胃口了
Kills the craving.
-好用吗  -当然了
- And that works? - You betcha.
对什么都好使  除了咸味焦糖
On everything except... salted caramel.
真好玩
Well, that's cute.
但我想的
But I was thinking
是这样的东西
something a little bit more like this.
你说不会再死人了
You said no one else was dying.
是盐弹
Salt pellets.
怎么回事
What's going on?
可怜人不该被关起来
Poor thing doesn't deserve to be locked up.
那就放她走啊
So let her go.
没人看到她的脸啊
No one saw her face, right?
嗯  凶手就是个流浪汉  打倒了你  逃走了
Yeah, he was a drifter, overpowered you, escaped.
太伤妹子自尊了啊
Well, there's some female empowerment for ya.
别担心  亲爱的
Don't worry, hon.
就问你几个问题
Just gonna ask you a few questions,
然后你就可以走了
Then you're free to go.
真的吗
I am?
保证
Scout's honor.
你记得自己袭击埃文斯教练吗
You remember attacking Coach Evans?
不记得  我发誓
No, I swear.
我去取新的吉祥物服装
I went to pick up the new mascot costume,
然后试了一下  紧接着
went to try it on, and the next thing I know...
我就在监狱里了
I'm in jail.
你认识他吗
Did you even know him?
他上学期是我的体育课教练
He was my P.E. coach last semester.
他挺严厉的  但是
I mean, he was kind of a hard-ass, but...
那不代表我希望他死
That doesn't mean that I wanted him dead.
米歇尔  你的服装哪来的
Michelle, where did you get the costume?
是旧货店吗
Was it a thrift store?
不  是有人捐给学校的
No, someone donated it to the school.
知道是谁吗
Do you know who?
丽塔·约翰逊
Rita Johnson?
嗯  你们是
Yeah, who's askin'?
我们有几个关于镇上一桩案子的问题要问你
Got a few questions we want to ask you about a case in town.
谁啊  妈妈
Who is it, mom?
麦克斯  回去完成作业吧
Um, Max, why don't you go back and finish your homework?
警察为什么来了
Why are the police here?
小伙子  见过真正的警车吗
Hey there, fella. You ever see a real cop car?
如果你妈不介意的话
I mean, if it's okay with your mom.
嗯
Yeah.
去吧
-你可以用警用无线电  -真的
- You can talk on the police radio. - Really?
-很容易学的  -太棒了
- It's pretty simple to figure out. - Cool.
我们能进去吗
Mind if we come inside?
服装是我弟弟  切斯特的
The costumes belonged to my brother Chester.
他生前是个儿童派对表演者
He was a kids' party performer before he passed.
切斯特是怎么死的
And, um, how did... how did Chester die?
我弟弟患有抑郁症
Uh, my brother suffered from depression.
几个月前自杀了
He took his own life a couple months back.
跳桥
Jumped off a bridge.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
麦克斯求我留下服装的
Max begged me to keep the costumes.
他很喜欢  他爱他舅舅
He loved them. He loved his uncle.
因为我们一起住  所以他们很亲
I mean, he lived with us, so they were really close.
但我看了只觉得伤心  于是就捐出去了
But they made me sad, so I donated them
捐给了本地高中  剧团
to the local high school, the theater company.
还有旧货店吗
Thrift shop?
嗯  都是那种地方
Yeah, places like that.
能问问切斯特葬在哪吗
Can I ask where Chester's buried?
没有土葬  是火葬
He's not. He was cremated.
能给他的服装列个清单吗
Would you mind making a list of his costumes?
能记得多少是多少
As many as you can remember?
好  但这跟你们的案子有什么关系
Sure. But what does this have to do with your case?
我们也想查清楚
That's what we're trying to figure out.
还有个问题
Uh, one more question.
切斯特跟斯坦·辛克尔或菲尔·埃文斯有过结吗
Did Chester have a falling out with Stan Hinkle or Phil Evans?
或者是任何人
Um, or anyone for that matter?
什么意思
What do you mean?
他有什么
Did he, um,
他跟谁有什么未了结的事吗
did he have any unfinished business with anyone?
没有  我觉得没有
No, not that I can think of.
我都...
I mean, I don't even...
我觉得切斯特都不认识这俩人
I don't think Chester even knew those guys.
我记得切斯特的自杀案
I remember Chester's suicide.
很可悲
Real sad.
现在我们知道他就是那个鬼魂
So now that we know he's the ghost,
我们怎么制止他
how do we stop him?
一般是要烧掉尸骨
Well, usually you gotta burn their bones,
但他是火葬的
but he was cremated.
那么我们是没办法喽
So we're up poop's creek without a paddle?
也不算
Mm. Not exactly.
他似乎是附在服装上了
I mean, looks like he's tied to the costumes,
那么想阻止他  就得烧掉服装
which means the only way to stop him is to burn them.
那我们已经领先了
Then we're already ahead of the game.
我让道格去高中取服装了
I had Doug go to the high school and collect the costumes.
太好了
Great.
这是其他的
Here is a list of the rest.
你和道格能给收集来吗
Think you and Doug can round 'em up?
当然
Yeah. You betcha.
那我们只需要查清切斯特跟被害人什么仇怨了
Now we just gotta figure out what Chester's beef was with the vics.
鬼魂一般为私事回来纠缠活人
Ghosts come back for something personal.
通常是复仇
Usually, it's revenge.
送我去医院
All right, drop me off at the hospital.
我去看看教练
I'll check on the coach.
我去找找斯坦的遗孀  走吧
I'll see if I can find Stan's widow. Let's go.
你是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
你问出什么来了吗
You get a story out of bozo?
嗯  他叫史蒂夫·布勒斯
Yeah, uh, name is Steve Buress.
60岁了  退休医师
60 years old, retired G.P.
据说是在跟孙子玩变装
Apparently, he was playing dress-up with his grandson,
紧接着就...
and the next thing he knew, he...
都不知道自己怎么来到医院的
Doesn't even know how he got to the hospital.
他也"逃"了吧
He "escape," too?
嗯
Yeah.
我绝对要丢掉饭碗了
I'm so losing my job.
我正往伍德伯里去拿一套啄木鸟的服装
I was on my way to Woodbury to pick up a woodpecker costume.
然后就听说了教练的事
Then I got the call about the coach.
嗯  这次是
Yeah. This time...
杀人小丑
Killer clown.
已经发布了通告
Already put out an A.P.B.
这小镇是怎么了
What the heck is going on in this doggone town?
我说了  模仿犯啊
Told ya. Copycat killers.
这是模仿模仿犯的模仿犯吗
So this is a-a copycat of a copycat?
得了  道格
Come on, Doug.
没那么难理解吧
It's not that hard to wrap your noggin around, is it?
听你的  警长
Whatever you say, sheriff.
我去取那套啄木鸟了
I'm gonna go get the woodpecker.
怎么回事  你不能好好对他一次吗
What's the deal? Why don't you cut the guy a break?
换了我也不信你那套啊
I mean, I wouldn't be buying what you're selling either.
我没时间应付不服管的人
I don't have time for insubordination.
或许你是因为老道格而迁怒新道格
Or is it maybe that you're treating new Doug like old Doug
连个机会都不给他
and not even giving him a chance?
知道我怎么想吗
You know what I think?
你该少管闲事
You need to mind your own beeswax.
我们还得破案呢
We have a case to solve.
菲尔和斯坦是大学室友
Phil and Stan were college roommates.
18岁就认识了
Knew each other since they were 18.
像兄弟一样亲
They were like brothers.
这么多年的交情
Out of all these years of friendship,
你丈夫或教练认不认识
did, uh, your husband or the coach ever know a guy
一个切斯特·约翰逊
by the name of Chester Johnson?
是个儿童派对表演者
He was a children's performer.
嗯  认识
Yeah. They knew.
我都不想说他的名字
I can't even say his name.
他让我恶心
He makes me sick.
我知道不该说死人的坏话
I know you shouldn't speak ill of the dead,
但对那人  我没有任何好话
but I have nothing nice to say about that man.
杀人小丑  真的吗
Killer clown? You're serious?
不  迪恩  我开玩笑呢
No, Dean, I'm joking.
因为我可喜欢小丑了
Because clowns are really funny to me.
-你搞定了吗  -搞定了
- Did you take care of it? - Yeah.
你呢  有发现吗
What about you? Anything?
有  原来斯坦和教练
Yeah, turns out that Stan and the coach
早就是死党了
were besties from way back
他们曾指控切斯特跟他们的孩子们过于亲密了
who accused Chester of crossing the line with their kids.
嗯
Yeah.
但他们没去找警察
But they didn't wanna go to the cops
因为不想让他们的孩子们尴尬
'cause they didn't wanna embarrass their kids.
于是他们决定自己去追踪切斯特
So they decided to track down Chester themselves.
他们去了他家  却见到了丽塔
They went to his house and got Rita instead.
这么说她说谎了  切斯特其实认识被害人
So she lied? Chester did know the vics?
看来是的  芙兰说丽塔让他们滚蛋
Apparently. So Fran said that Rita told them to screw off.
然后  他们还没机会跟他正面交锋
And...Well, before they had a chance to confront him,
他就自杀了
he killed himself.
那么  是自杀导致了复仇鬼魂
So suicide led to a vengeful spirit.
咱们以前也不是没见过这种情况
I mean, it's not like we haven't seen it before.
也可能不是自杀
Or maybe it wasn't suicide.
你是麦克斯  对吧
Hey, uh, Max, right?
你妈妈在家吗
Is, uh, is your mom home?
-还没回来  -好吧
- Not yet. - Okay.
我只想再问她几个问题
Um, I just needed to ask her a few more questions.
那你就进来等吧
I-I guess you can wait inside.
好
Okay.
扑克啊
Poker?
我能教你一两招
I can show you a move or two.
小魔术
Magic trick.
我舅舅教我的
Something my uncle taught me.
你跟他挺亲的  是吧
Yeah, you were pretty close to him, huh?
对
Yeah.
他很酷  我很想他
He was cool. I miss him.
他听起来像个好人
He sounds like a good guy.
他就是好人
He was.
那些人说他的事  不是真的
What those men said about him wasn't true.
我不喜欢你趁我不在家的时候
I don't appreciate you talking to my son
跟我儿子说话
when I am not home.
我们只是在交流一些纸牌技巧  仅此而已
Hey, we were just trading some card tricks, that's all.
你来干什么  我知道的都告诉你了
What are you even doing here? I told you everything I know.
好了  亲爱的  回你房间去
Okay, honey, go to your room.
听着  我们知道
Look, we know
教练和斯坦因为切斯特的事找过你
that the coach and Stan confronted you about Chester.
那跟你们没有半点关系
That is none of your damn business.
那跟这一切都没关系
It has nothing to do with any of this.
那些人被杀了
Those men were murdered.
不管你信不信  你弟弟跟这事有关
And whether or not you believe it, your brother is connected.
怎么会  切斯特已经死了  他自杀了
How? Chester is dead. Killed himself.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
听着  我们得知道真相
Look, we need to know the truth.
这事关人命
People's lives are at stake here.
没错  甚至是你的命  麦克斯的命
Yeah. Maybe yours. Maybe Max's.
好吧
Okay.
几个月前  斯坦和教练来过
A couple of months ago, Stan and the coach came by.
他们说切斯特对他们的孩子们
They said that Chester was with their kids,
做了些
did something...
不合适的事
inappropriate.
我选择了维护亲人
I got defensive. I mean...
切斯特人很好  对麦克斯就像父亲一样
Chester was sweet, like a dad to Max.
所以我让他们滚蛋
So I told them to get lost.
要是他们对切斯特有意见  可以去找警察
If they had a problem with Chester, they could go to the cops.
可他们没有
But they didn't.
他们没有任何证据
They didn't have any evidence.
但接下来  我也开始怀疑了
But then, I started to have my doubts.
虽然我很想维护我弟弟
I mean, as much as I wanted to defend my brother...
但他们说的实在...
What they said really...
让我如鲠在喉
got under my skin.
切斯特一直有点...不合群
Chester was always a little... Off.
只跟孩子们处得来
Only got along with kids.
所以他才会做派对表演者
That's why he became a party performer.
我一辈子都在维护我弟弟
I spent my whole life sticking up for my brother.
可要是我没看清他的真面目呢
But what if I couldn't see him for who he really was?
而且他跟麦克斯那么亲近
And he and Max were so close.
我是说
I mean...
要是他一直在伤害他  而我不知道呢
what if he was hurting him, and I didn't know?
切斯特是我弟弟  可是...
Chester was my brother, but...
麦克斯是我儿子
Max is my son.
所以你想保护他
So you wanted to protect him?
我不能视而不见啊
How could I look the other way?
我必须鼓起勇气面对我最害怕的事
I had to suck it up and face my biggest fear.
我不做  还有谁呢
If not me, then who?
但我应该和他谈谈的
But I should've talked to him.
我应该先去找他的
I just should've gone to him first.
但是...
Instead...
我却把斯坦叫回来了
I called Stan back.
然后他说他们会搞定的
And he said that they would take care of it.
(松景中学)
有天切斯特去表演的时候
So one day when Chester was working,
我把他的行踪告诉了他们
I told them where he was.
去哪啊
Going somewhere?
是啊  回家
Yeah. Home.
别指望了
I don't think so.
不要
No.
救命  救命
Help! Help!
他们保证我不会伤害切斯特的
They promised me that they weren't gonna hurt Chester.
就只是吓唬吓唬他而已
They were just gonna scare him a little bit.
我还想  也许好好吓他一顿...
And I thought, you know, maybe a good scare..,
他就安生了
maybe that's all he needed.
住手  住手  求你们了
Stop! Stop, please!
住手  你们为什么要这么做
Stop! Why are you doing this?!
你知道为什么  变态
You know why, sicko!
离我们的孩子远一点
Leave our kids alone!
我从没伤害过你们的孩子
I've never hurt your kids
或者任何人的孩子
or anyone's kids!
我喜欢小孩
I love kids!
是啊  我们知道
Yeah, we know!
放开我  放开我
Let me go. Let me go!
-别动  我们不会...  -放开我
- Stop it! We're not gonna -- - Let me go!
-别动了  我们不...  -放开我
- Stop it! We won't -- - Let me go!
-放开我  -别乱动  别乱动
- Oh, let me go! - Stop it! Stop it!
他们不是有意要杀他的  他们说...
They didn't mean to kill him. They -- they said...
那是场意外
that it was an accident.
但我当时又不在场  所以也不知道真相
But I wasn't there, so I didn't know what to believe.
我本想去找警察  把事情解释清楚
And I wanted to go to the cops and explain what happened,
但斯坦说我们都会进监狱的
but Stan said that we'd all go to jail.
我不能那样对麦克斯
And I couldn't do that to Max.
他已经失去了父亲
He already lost his father
还有舅舅
and his uncle.
他不能再失去我了
And he... he couldn't lose me, too.
所以我...保持了沉默
So I...didn't say anything.
恐惧会让人无力
Fear cripples you.
让人袖手旁观
It makes you do nothing.
或者更糟...
Or worse...
让人做出会令自己后悔的事
it makes you do something that you regret.
我本该相信我弟弟的
I should've trusted my brother.
怎样了
How's it going?
所有服装都找到了
Tracked down every last costume.
你不会碰巧看见了一个鹿头吧
You didn't happen to see a-a deer head by chance, did you?
鹿头
Deer head?
天呐
Oh, my god.
单子上没有啊
That wasn't on the list.
麦克斯
Max?
麦克斯  麦克斯
Max? Max?
Max? Max!
麦克斯  麦克斯  不要
Max. Max, no!
你在干什么  麦克斯
What are you doing? M-max!
麦克斯
Max?
妈妈  发生什么事了
Mom, what's happening?
快拿去烧了
Burn it now!
好的
Yeah.
跟我来
Come with me.
好了  无论如何  待在这个圈里
Okay. Whatever you do, stay inside this circle.
-我不明白  -有鬼
- I don't understand. - Ghosts.
你想知道这事怎么跟你弟弟有关吗
You wanna know how this ties to your brother?
因果报应
Cause and effect.
含冤而亡就会催生复仇鬼魂
Wrongful death spawns a vengeful spirit.
切斯特
Chester.
切斯特舅舅  不要
Uncle Chester, no!
好了  我们该...
All right, I think it's, uh,
离开这里了
time we gotta get out of here.
希望你们下次再来明尼苏达州
Here's hoping something less murderous
是因为不这么凶残的事
brings you back to Minnesota,
比如普林斯(爵士歌手)或者奶酪块节
like Prince or Cheese Curd Fest.
"块"这字戳中我了
You had me at "curd."
我不知道你俩是怎么做到的
I-I don't know how you two do this,
日复一日
day in, day out.
调查谁被附身  谁没被附身
Figuring out who's possessed, who isn't.
你们的生活简直就像一坨屎  是吧
Your life's one big poop storm, isn't it?
这话真有猎人的样
Spoken like a true hunter.
真的吗
Really?
-猎人  -是啊
- Hunter? - Oh, yeah.
你已经解决了三个案子
I mean, with three cases under your belt,
我觉得这是你应得的称呼
I think you earned it.
好了
Okay.
嗯
Yeah.
好了好了
There we go.
谢谢
Thank you.
拜
Bye.
那个
So...
这几天真疯狂
Been a crazy couple of days.
的确如此
Darn tootin'.
但你做的很好
But you've been great.
我真的非常感谢你的努力
I really appreciate all your hard work.
还有
And, uh...
抱歉我对你有些严厉
Sorry if I was a little tough on ya.
你是说把我当做出气筒吗
You mean you treating me like a punching bag?
没关系 真的
It's okay. Really.
我也有包袱的  唐娜
I got baggage, too, Donna.
大家都有
Everyone does.
如果能让你好受些的话
You know, if it makes you feel any better,
你可以叫我的中间名
you can call me by my middle name...
朗尼
Lonnie.
我觉得道格就行了
I think "Doug" will do just fine.
好吧
Okay.
我还继续向上帝祈祷  因为如果是上帝
I keep praying to God because if it is God --
我知道你觉得不是  但如果是
and I know you think it isn't, but if it is --
那么他给我看的幻觉  我不知道该怎么办
then he's showing me something I don't know what to do with.
是什么
What?
笼子
The cage.
路西法的笼子
Lucifer's cage?
嗯
Yeah.
如果他是告诉我  我必须回去怎么办
What if he's telling me I have to go back?
如果他是要说  打败黑暗的办法
What if he's saying that's where the answer is
就是这个  怎么办
to beating the darkness?
萨姆  不是  不是  好吗
Sam, no. No, okay.
我不知道这些幻觉是不是上帝给的
I don't know if these visions are coming from God
还是公共电视网什么的
or PBS or what.
但我们已经试过那条路了
But we've been down that road.
和那笼子有关的  就是自杀行为
Anything having to do with that cage is -- it -- it's suicide.
你最了解了
And you of all people know that.
所以不行
So, no.
绝对不行
Just...not gonna happen.
好吧
Okay.
好